## **ABOUT ME**

My name is Jarosław Janas and I'm a Front-End Developer. I started my work with code in 2020. I really enjoy it and I want to be a better Web-Developer every day. My specialization is creating websites and applications in JavaScript language.

# **EXPERIENCE**

2021 - NOW



### Front-End Developer – Freelancer

- https://www.demo-transfers.vercel.app app demo version. The project was bought by several companies.
- https://www.focuseye.pl
- https://www.pyszotka.pl
- https://www.veloway.pl
- https://www.sosniegorne.pl
- https://www.hotelmiodowa.pl
- https://www.telefonygorlice.pl
- https://listazakupy.netlify.app

...more in my portfolio on www.jarekjanas.com

2019 - NOW



Hotel Receptionist - Hotel Miodowa\*\*\*

Cracow

checking reservations, service for hotel guests, taking care of the positive image of the hotel

2017 - 2018



Soldier of Polish Army – 22<sup>nd</sup> Mountain Infantry Battalion

Kłodzko

military service for the country

### **EDUCATION**

2020 - NOW



Front-End Developer – Courses on the UDEMY e-learning platform

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT, REACT ROUTER, REDUX, NEXT.JS

2017 - 2019



Master Degree – Pedagogical University of Cracow

education for security and crisis management

2014 - 2017



Bachelor Degree – Pedagogical University of Cracow

national security



**Jarosław Janas** 

### CONTACT

+48 798 194 305



jarekjanas95@gmail.com



www.jarekjanas.com



Cracow 31-222, Poland

### **SKILLS**

### **Professional:**



HTML



GH



CSS



STYLE C.

JS

**JAVASCRIPT** 



REDUX



REACT



**NEXT.JS** 

## **Personal:**

- CREATIVITY
- SELF-MOTIVATION
- TEAM WORK
- SCRUPULOUSNESS

#### Languages:

- POLISH
- ENGLISH